http://www.diogenesllc.com/privacy.html

PRIVACY AND SECURITY NOTICE Thank you for visiting the Diogenes LLC web site and reviewing our privacy and security notice. We remind you that if you link to a site outside of the Diogenes LLC web site, you are subject to the policies of the new site.Here is how we handle information about your visit to our web site or exchanged with our agency:            A.    Information Collected and Stored Automatically                  If you visit our site to read or download information, we collect and store the                following information about your  visit: -   The name of the Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or  "yourschool.edu" if you are connecting from a university's domain) and the IP address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you are using the Internet) from which you access our site;-    The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;-    The date and time you access our site; -    The Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site; and-    The pages you visit and the information you request. This information is primarily collected for statistical analysis and technical improvements to the site. This computer system uses software programs to create summary statistics, which may be used for such purposes as assessing what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. In certain circumstances, however, we may take additional steps to identify you based on this information and we may share this information, including your identity, with government agencies.  B.   If You Send Us Personal Information If you choose to provide us with personal information, such as by sending an e-mail or by filling out a form and submitting it through our Web site, we will use that information to respond to your message or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Remember that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. If your communication is sensitive or includes personal information you may prefer to send it encrypted or by postal mail instead.
We may share the information you give us with a government agency if your inquiry relates to that agency. In other limited circumstances, such as responses to requests from Congress and private individuals, we may be required by law to disclose information you submit. Before you submit personal information, such as on an online form, you may be given more specific guidance as to how your personal information may be used. Electronically submitted information is maintained and destroyed according to the legal requirements for the State of Connecticut and/or Federal Statutes.  C.   Cookies "Cookies" are small bits of text that are either used for the duration of a session ("session cookies"), or saved on a user's hard drive in order to identify that user, or information about that user, the next time the user logs on to a Web site ("persistent cookies"). Diogenes LLC web site does not use cookies. SECURITY For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Anyone using this system expressly consents to such monitoring and is advised that if such monitoring reveals evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, such evidence may be provided to appropriate law enforcement officials. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information on this server are strictly prohibited and may be punishable by law, including the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act of 1996.SAFEGUARDING OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONCT Public Act 08-167Diogenes LLC complies with CT Public Act 08-167 (Safeguarding of Personal Information).
Protected information, as defined by the act and/or Federal Law, will be maintianed and/or transmitted in a manner consitent with state and federal law.
Clients are responsible to secure all protected infomation received in a manner that is consistent with the law.To learn more, you may contact us by telephone (203.264.6802) or
via email.Close this Window to return to the Services Page.home | about us | services | resources | contact us
